[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert DeNiro and Danny DeVito were first considered for the roles of burglars Harry and Marv in the hilarious movie Home Alone.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2001 William Wesley film involves a chain gang.", "correct_answer": "Route 666", "incorrect_answers": ["The Roost", "Night of the Comet", "Land of the Dead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Walt Disney animated movie was released in 1989 and became one of the most successful films of the year.", "correct_answer": "The Little Mermaid", "incorrect_answers": ["Cinderella", "Beauty and the Beast", "Sleeping Beauty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The words Stick that in your trophy case were said by both Burt Reynolds and Adam Sandler in The Longest Yard and its 2005 remake, respectively.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This space object, named after the mythological son of Ares (Mars), is the larger and innermost of Mars two moons, orbiting closer to its major planet than any other satellite in the Solar System.", "correct_answer": "Phobos", "incorrect_answers": ["Thebe", "Elara", "Deimos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the recommended beneficial daily dose of wine.", "correct_answer": "One to two glasses", "incorrect_answers": ["Five glasses", "Three to four glasses", "Six glasses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the color of the blossoms of the apple tree?", "correct_answer": "White and pink", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "Purple and yellow", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the twin look-a-like of Queen Amidala in The Phantom Menace?", "correct_answer": "Keira Knightley", "incorrect_answers": ["Kate Bosworth", "Jennifer Garner", "Christina Milian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of which island is also a computer programming language name?", "correct_answer": "Java", "incorrect_answers": ["Cuba", "Jamaica", "Malta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which drug consists of a sediment, extracted form the fruit of the squirting cucumber, that is native of the the Mediterranean region?", "correct_answer": "Elaterium", "incorrect_answers": ["Piperazine", "Thionin", "Mycoherbicide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the World Series first broadcast on radio?", "correct_answer": "1922", "incorrect_answers": ["1932", "1912", "1942"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Highly coveted bulbs of a member of the Liliaceae family, caused this in the Netherlands in the early 17th century.", "correct_answer": "Tulipomania", "incorrect_answers": ["Tulipation", "Tulip Madness", "Tulipancy"]}]